[Music]
soggy log June 1st I've ridden 250 miles
in the last 2 days and we've only raised
$10,000 it's only enough to send a 100
goats to families in Africa how do I get
people excited about this Mission maybe
I just haven't done enough for people
right here in the good old us OFA time
to change
that P Water craft P Water craft P Water
craft P Water
craft so we met Kaye the night before
and Kaye tells us that she's graduating
from high school the next day and we're
just like oh Kaye oh do you want to ride
a jet ski to
graduation and Kaylee's like yes I
do like a caterpillar coming out of a
cocoon a high school graduation is maybe
the most important time of a young
lady's life until she experiences
anything after that hey Kaye hey you're
my ride aren't you I'm your ride all
right all right get on here you're going
to graduate
hey welcome to being an adult it's all
as good as
B Kay is ready to get wasted tonight
hell yeah hell yeah hell yeah no more
school no more school no more school you
can do anything you want who you going
to vote for now I don't even know
politics who gives a
kayy what are you going to be when
you grow up a nurse
practitioner now that you're 18 you can
totally milk a cow cow you legally can
milk a cow that's one of the laws of the
United States are you in dead serious uh
no oh no no I think you can milk cow
whenever you want okay and then I drop
her off at graduation you know like
ready for her to just transform into the
nurse practitioner she was always meant
to be and it was like my jety had become
this like weird wet cocoon you know and
Kay had got on a caterpillar and got off
a butterfly destined to get wasted in
the woods was
beautiful and then the whole thing was
we're going to go to casasia casasia is
the smallest town in Illinois and it's
fascinating this place used to have
thousands of people and then the
Mississippi changed Direction around it
and killed everyone in the town and now
there's 14 people left and then I'm
going to give them this present like I
have a big surprise for everybody here
we are in a Cas casasia I'm going to try
and meet every single person in casasia
and give him a bun cake and I invite
them to uh the gift that I I'm giving to
the
[Music]
town my camera good for you I've got a
bunp CI for everybody just as a gift hey
dog I'm coming shooting
picture I've got a bunt cake for
everybody who lives in casasia well
thank you you're welcome I've got
cameras just following me because I'm
jet skiing from Chicago to New Orleans
and I happened to stop in casasi and I
found out that it was the second
smallest town in Illinois there's only
three five maybe eight of us that lives
here I thought it was 14 so you guys are
the smallest town in illin some moved
out oh yeah someone moved out you
actually got it back to the smallest
town have a good day yeah you
too only eight so what's interesting is
talk to that lady eight people there's
only eight people which is perfect cuz
we only have nine bun cakes so I think
we could literally meet every want
here's a house let's see if anybody's
home hi Hi how are you we're good you
good I'm just going around trying to
meet everybody in Casas and I wanted to
uh give you this bun cake okay well sure
thank you well apprciate it I brought
you a bun cake oh well they're delicious
yes there you go he belongs to a
neighbor down the
street this town used to have
7,000 people in it and then the
Mississippi River changed Direction
around it wiping it out and it's only
because of one piece of of concrete that
it doesn't successfully destroy it every
year but then every 20 years it does
never been to a a house that starts on
the Second Story hello hello bun cake
delivery thanks guys thanks take care so
everybody's been pretty overwhelmingly
friendly I was more expecting like if
you live in a town with 14 people that
you kind of maybe hate people but maybe
it's the opposite it's a choice because
you want to live somewhere that you love
and I respect that I like that a lot
it feels weird saying to everybody
without telling them what it is I got
you a gift it sounds like I'm a a
lunatic
but I I don't want to tell him what it
is I want him to be
surprised all right on count of three
you're going to turn around and we will
reveal the gift to
casasia one two three turn
[Applause]
around kitties Mary hey how did you
happen to get cat she's our cat person
that'll be up there at least for a month
that's great well thank you so much
thank you guys so much thank you guys so
much let's get let's pull it in for Cas
the biggest little T illino put it in 1
2 3 1 2 3
Casia these people live in a town that
completely floods every 20 years I mean
I expected to either find like grade a
lunatics or morons like a bunch
of dumb Birds who keep making their
nests in a cannon you know but instead I
found the kindest people people who
loved where they lived even if it might
kill them and I get that that's cool
like I'm from Jersey we're the same way
right on Cas Casia long live the
boss Cas cas help me a lot if you just
reach out to people don't be scared to
talk to them even if they only live in a
town with eight people they're still
going to be very happy to have a
conversation with you especially if
you've got a
[Music]
[Laughter]
cake
[Music]
hey Africa needs bun cakes too America
so donate click right here and donate to
heer come on what are you waiting
for